Guide to the William Bronk Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
William Bronk Papers
1908-1999.
Bronk, William.
45 linear ft (ca.40,000 items in 95 boxes & 1 oversize folder)
Columbia University Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Butler Library, New York, NY 10027.
4079737
History
American poet; born in 1918 in Fort Edward, N.Y. and was the author of more than 15 books of poems and essays and a winner of the American Book Award in 1982. William Bronk died on 22 Feb 1999.
Scope and Content
Correspondence, manuscripts, audio cassettes, photographs, and printed materials. The correspondence covers the years 1934 through 1999 and consists mostly of letters to and from James L. Weil, whose Elizabeth Press was Bronk's publisher from 1969 to 1981, from Eugene Canadé, an artist who illustrated many of Bronk's books, from Bronk's sisters, and from many friends. There are also letters from W.H. Auden; Paul Auster, Cid Corman (Bronk's first publisher and founder of ORIGIN, the magazine in which many of Bronk's early poems first appeared), Robert Creeley, Samuel French Morse, Gilbert Sorrentino, and many other well-known authors. The manuscripts include notebooks and binders containing handwritten and typed drafts of poems and essays. They document nearly all of Bronk's published writings including the collection of essays he completed in the 1940s which was published in 1980 as THE BROTHER IN ELYSIUM as well as the collection of poems published in 1981 as LIFE SUPPORTS: NEW AND COLLECTED POEMS for which Bronk won the American Books Award in 1982. There are also page proofs, photographs of Bronk, many audio cassettes of Bronk reading his work in the 1970s and the 1980s and printed materials.
Arrangement
Selectively cataloged; remainder arranged: Boxes 1-9: Cataloged correspondence & manuscripts; Boxes 10-66: Uncataloged correspondence; Boxes 67-76: Uncataloged manuscripts by William Bronk; Boxes 77-89: Uncataloged manuscripts by others; Box 90: Photographs & tape cassettes; Boxes 91-95: Printed materials; & an Oversized folder.
Subjects
Elizabeth Press.; Allen, Donald, 1912-2004.; Atkinson, Brooks, 1894-1984.; Auden, W. H. (Wystan Hugh), 1907-1973.; Auster, Paul, 1947-; Benedikt, Michael, 1935-; Bly, Robert.; Brooks, Gwendolyn, 1917-2000.; Canade, Eugene G.; Clark, Tom, 1941-; Corman, Cid.; Cox, Sidney, 1889-1952.; Creeley, Robert, 1926-2005.; Cuomo, Mario Matthew.; De Vries, Peter.; Duncan, Robert, 1919-1988.; Economou, George.; Enslin, Theodore.; Eshleman, Clayton.; Hall, Donald, 1928-; Lowenfels, Walter, 1897-1976.; McCarthy, Eugene J., 1916-2005.; Mailer, Norman.; Moore, Marianne, 1887-1972.; Morse, Samuel French, 1916-; Mumford, Lewis, 1895-1990.; Olson, Charles, 1910-1970.; Oppen, George.; Oppenheimer, Joel.; Paz, Octavio, 1914-1998.; Pearson, Norman Holmes, 1909-1975.; Rahv, Philip, 1908-1973.; Randall, Margaret, 1936-; Rannit, Aleksis.; Sarton, May, 1912-1995.; Schulberg, Budd.; Shapiro, Karl Jay, 1913-2000.; Smith, William Jay, 1918-; Sorrentino, Gilbert.; Swallow, Alan, 1915-1966.; Tagliabue, John, 1923-; Tomlinson, Charles, 1927-; Turnbull, Gael.; Van Doren, Mark, 1894-1972.; Vas Dias, Robert.; Warren, Robert Penn, 1905-1989.; Weil, James L.; Williams, Jonathan, 1929-2008.; American essays--20th century.; American literature--20th century.; American poetry--New York (State); American poetry--20th century.; Authors, American--20th century.; Poetry, Modern--20th century.; Publishers and publishing--United States.; Authors and publishers--United States.; Small presses--United States.; Articles.; Audio cassettes.; Clippings.; Drafts (literary).; Essays.; Financial records.; Greeting cards.; Notebooks.; Photographs.; Photoprints.; Poems.; Proofs.; Authors.; Poets.; Origin.
Access Restrictions
This collection has no restrictions.
This collection is located on-site.
Acquisition
1989 M-1989 Papers Bronk, Willaim Gift
08/23/1990 M-90-08-23 Letters from Bronk to Weil Weil, James L. Gift
M-1991 Letters from Bronk to Weil Weil, James L. Gift
1990 M-1990 Letters from Bronk Lyman, Henry Gift
02/15/1991 M-91-02-15 Letters from Bronk Canadé, Eugene G. Gift
01/08/1994 M-94-01-08 Book Elman, Richard Gift
02/23/1996 M-96-02-23 Letters & printed items Lee, Elizabeth Clark Gift
06/28/1996 M-96-06-28 Letters from Bronk & others Weil, James L. Gift
10/14/1993 M-93-10-14 55 items re. Bronk Weil, James L. Gift
1999 M-1999 3 Bronk letters to Booth Booth, Philip Gift
07/07/1999 M-99-07-07 133 letters re. Bronk Weil, James L. Gift
02/28/2000 M-00-02-28 Letters to J. Weil re. W.Bronk Weil, James L. Gift
09/11/2000 M-09-11-00 50 Bronk letters to Mark Katzman AQZ7507 (Katzman) Purchase
Gift of William Bronk, 1989 & 1990.
Gift of the estate of Elizabeth Bronk.
Gift of Henry Lyman, 1990.
Gift of James L. Weil, 1990, 1991, 1993, 1996, 1999, & 2000.
Gift of Eugene G. Canadé, 1991.
Gift of Richard Elman, 1994.
Gift of Elizabeth Clark Lee, 1996.
Gift of Philip Booth, 1999.
Gift of the estate of William Bronk, 1999.
The finding aid is available in the repository and online.
- Series I: Cataloged Correspondence and Manuscripts
  - Allen, Donald M. (Box 1)
  - Atkinson, Brooks (Box 1)
  - Auden, Wystan Hugh (Box 1)
  - Auster, Paul (Box 1)
  - Benedikt, Michael (Box 1)
  - Bly, Robert E. (Box 1)
  - Bronk, William
    - 1934-1941 undated (Box 1)
    - 1942-1959 (Box 2)
    - 1960-1974 (Box 3)
    - 1975-1985 (Box 4)
    - 1986-1999 (Box 5)
  - Brooks, Gwendolyn (Box 6)
  - Clark, Tom (Box 6)
  - Corman,Cid
    - 1950-1971 (Box 6)
    - 1972-1999 (Box 7)
  - Cox, Sidney (Box 7)
  - Creeley, Robert (Box 7)
  - Cuomo, Mario M. (Box 7)
  - De Vries, Peter (Box 7)
  - Dias, Robert Vas (Box 7)
  - Duncan, Robert (Box 7)
  - Economou, George D. (Box 8)
  - Enslin, Theodore (Box 8)
  - Eshleman, Clayton (Box 8)
  - Hall, Donald (Box 8)
  - Lowenfels, Walter (Box 8)
  - McCarthy, Eugene J. (Box 8)
  - Mailer, Norman (Box 8)
  - Moore, Marianne (Box 8)
  - Mumford, Lewis (Box 8)
  - Olson, Charles (Box 8)
  - Oppen, George (Box 8)
  - Oppenheimer, Joel (Box 8)
  - Paz, Octavio (Box 8)
  - Rahv, Philip (Box 8)
  - Randall, Margaret (Box 8)
  - Rannit, Aleksis (Box 8)
  - Sarton, May (Box 9)
  - Schulberg, Budd (Box 9)
  - Shapiro, Karl (Box 9)
  - Smith, William Jay (Box 9)
  - Sorrentino, Gilbert (Box 9)
  - Swallow, Alan (Box 9)
  - Tagliabue, John (Box 9)
  - Tomlinson, Charles (Box 9)
  - Turnbull, Gael (Box 9)
  - Van Doren, Mark (Box 9)
  - Warren, Robert Perm (Box 9)
  - Williams, Jonathan (Box 9)
- Series II: Uncataloged Correspondence and related items
  - A (Box 10)
  - Ab-Am (Box 10)
  - The Academy of American Poets (New York NY) (Box 10)
  - An-Au (Box 10)
  - Andrew, Denis Y. (Box 10)
  - B (Box 10)
  - Ba-Bi (Box 10)
  - Bartlett, Pontiff, Stewart & Rhodes, P.C., Attorneys at Law (Box 11)
  - Berl, Christine (Box 11)
  - Bertolf, Robert J. (Box 11)
  - Bl-Bo (Box 11)
  - Blodgett, Harold W. (Box 11)
  - Booth, Martin (Box 11)
  - Botnick, Ken (Box 11)
  - Br (Box 11)
  - Branson, Jean Rikhoff (Box 11)
  - Bronk, Elizabeth (1932-1990) (Box 12-14)
  - Bronk, Ethel Elizabeth Funston
    - 1934-1969 (Box 15)
    - 1970-1982 (Box 16)
  - Bronk, William M., Sr. (Box 16)
  - Bronk family (Box 16)
  - Brooks, Alfred & Maxine Munt (Box 16)
  - Brown, Laura G. (Box 16)
  - Bu-By (Box 16)
  - Buckeye, Robert (Box 16)
  - Bullock, Sheldon Edward Michael (Box 16)
  - Bushnell, Sterling S. & Marion (Box 16)
  - Canadé, Eugene G, & family (Box 17)
  - C (Box 18)
  - Ca (Box 18)
  - Carella, Richard A. (Box 18)
  - Carlson family (Box 18)
  - Carman, Paul (Box 18)
  - Cesari, Gene S. (Box 18)
  - Ch-Ci (Box 18)
  - Chamberlain, Peggy & Baxter (Box 18)
  - Chawla, Louise (Box 18)
  - Christie, Jane Elizabeth (Box 18)
  - Cl-Co (Box 19)
  - The Clara Laughlin Travel Service, Inc. (New York NY) (Box 19)
  - Clarke, Shirley (Box 19)
  - Clippinger, David W. (Box 19)
  - Cogan, Robert (Box 19)
  - Coggeshall, Calvert (Box 19)
  - Collins, Ronald W. (Box 19)
  - Columbia University (Box 19)
  - Constance, Douglas Craig (Box 19)
  - Corrigan, Paul (Box 19)
  - Councilor, Jane Bronk (Mrs. James A.)
    - 1932-1971 (Box 20)
    - 1972-1992 (Box 21)
  - Councilor family (Box 22)
  - Cox, Alice R. (Mrs. Sidney) (Box 22)
  - Cr-Cu (Box 22)
  - Creative Artists Public Service Program (New York NY) (Box 22)
  - Crandall Library (Glens Falls NY) (Box 22)
  - Cronkhite, George Ferris (Box 22)
  - Cuddihy, Michael (Box 22)
  - Cummington Community of the Arts (Cummington MA) (Box 23)
  - D (Box 23)
  - Dartmouth College (Hanover NH) (Box 23)
  - Davies, Jordan (Box 24)
  - Davis, Dale (Box 24)
  - Davis, Lydia (Box 24)
  - De Blasiis, Giovannina Maria (Box 24)
  - Degnan, June Oppen (Box 24)
  - Delbanco, Nicholas (Box 25)
  - Dobrin, Arthur (Box 25)
  - Drachler, Rose (Box 25)
  - Dube, Mr & Mrs Bertram J. (Box 25)
  - Dufault, Peter Kane (Box 25)
  - DuVall, Jack (Box 25)
  - E (Box 26)
  - Easton, Ronca & Edward R. (Box 26)
  - Elman, Richard M.
    - 1965-1981 (Box 26)
    - 1981-1996 (Box 27)
  - L'Ensemble (Cambridge NY) (Box 28)
  - Erdmann, Martin J. (Box 28)
  - Ernest, John Richard & Rebecca M. (Box 28)
  - Evans, William R. & Eileen (Box 28)
  - Ewart, William B. (Box 29)
  - F (Box 29)
  - Fa-Fl (Box 29)
  - Faivre, Rob (Box 29)
  - Farrar, Straus & Giroux, Inc., Book Publishers (Box 29)
  - Feld, Ross (Box 29)
  - Finkelstein, Norman M. (Box 29)
  - Flaherty, Joseph F. (Box 30)
  - Fleckenstein, Daniel L. (Box 30)
  - Fo-Fy (Box 30)
  - Foster, Ed (Box 30)
  - Freeman, John (Box 31)
  - French, Loren K. (Box 31)
  - G (Box 31)
  - Ga-Gl (Box 31)
  - Gach, Cary G. (Box 31)
  - GeNoaNewYork Poetry and Interpretation. (1980) (Box 31)
  - Giessel, William U. (Box 32)
  - Gilmore, Charles Randall (Box 33)
  - Glass, Jesse (Box 33)
  - Glick, Wendell (Box 33)
  - Go-Gu (Box 33)
  - Goss, James (Box 33)
  - Graves, Bradford (Box 33)
  - Grealish, Gerard (Box 34)
  - Greene, Jonathan (Box 34)
  - Greenlaw, Laura B. (Box 34)
  - H (Box 34)
  - Ha (Box 34)
  - Haberman, Daniel (Box 34)
  - Hall, Mary E. (Mrs. Richard C.) (Box 34)
  - Hanks, Don (Box 35)
  - Harpold, Penelope S. (Box 35)
  - Harris, Marguerite (Box 35)
  - Harvard University (Box 35)
  - Hawley, Robert L. (Box 35)
  - Hazo, Samuel (Box 35)
  - He-Hi (Box 35)
  - Heidorf, Amelia G. (Box 35)
  - Heller, Michael (Box 35)
  - Hille, Randolph (Box 35)
  - Ho-Hu (Box 35)
  - Homer, John (Box 35)
  - Homer, Peter John (Box 35)
  - Horrigan, Edward Timothy (Box 35)
  - The Hyde Collection (Glens Falls NY) (Box 35)
  - I (Box 36)
  - I-J (Box 36)
  - J (Box 36)
  - Jevremovic, George (Box 36)
  - Johnson, Jenni (Box 36)
  - Johnson, Nicholas (Box 36)
  - Johnson, Ronald R. (Box 36)
  - Jordan, Clarke H. (Box 36)
  - K (Box 36)
  - Katzman, Mark Alan (Box 37)
  - Kearns, Sherry (Box 37)
  - Keffer, Steven L. & Sallie B. King (Box 37)
  - Keineg, Poal (Box 37)
  - Kelleher, John Vincent (Box 37)
  - Kelly. Edward P. & Anne ("Nancy") (Box 38)
  - Kimmelman, Burt (Box 38)
  - King, Martin R. (Box 38)
  - L (Box 38)
  - Lake George Arts Project (Box 39)
  - Lannan Foundation (Los Angeles) (Box 39)
  - Lape, Walter (Box 39)
  - Lathrop, Hubbel & Dorothy L. (Box 39)
  - Leary, Daniel (Box 39)
  - Lee, Elizabeth Bennett Clark (Box 39)
  - Levy, John (Box 39)
  - Lo-Ly (Box 40)
  - The Loft Press (Glens Falls NY) (Box 40)
  - Longstreet, Grant (Box 40)
  - Longville, Tim (Box 40)
  - Lowy, Steve (Box 40)
  - Lyman, Henry (Box 40)
  - Lyman, John (Box 40)
  - Lutes, Linda (Box 40)
  - M (Box 40)
  - Ma (Box 40)
  - Maril, Herman & Esta (Box 41)
  - Martin, William A. (Box 42)
  - Me-Mi (Box 42)
  - Mele, Jim (Box 42)
  - Mellor, David Williams (Box 42)
  - The Mettawee River Theatre Company (Box 42)
  - Meyer, Robert A. (Box 42)
  - Mi (Box 43)
  - Miller, Charles Henry (Box 43)
  - Miller, Stuart A. (Box 43)
  - Mitchell, Stephen (Box 43)
  - Mo-Mu (Box 43)
  - Mo (Box 43)
  - Moore, Sherry (Box 43)
  - Morse, Samuel French (Box 44)
  - Moyer Bell Limited (Mt. Kisco NY) (Box 44)
  - Muller, Elizabeth Cottenham & family (Box 44)
  - Murphy, Robert (Box 44)
  - N (Box 44)
  - Na-Ne (Box 44)
  - Nelson, Kent (Box 44)
  - New Directions (Box 44)
  - New York Foundation for the Arts (New York NY) (Box 45)
  - New York State Council on the Arts (New York NY) (Box 45)
  - The New Yorker (Box 45)
  - Newton, David (Box 45)
  - Nichols, George Douglas (Box 46)
  - No-Nu (Box 47)
  - North Point Press (Berkeley CA) (Box 47)
  - O (Box 48)
  - O'Neil, William P. (Box 48)
  - Oppen, George & Mary (Box 48)
  - Osborne, J. Ken (Box 48)
  - P (Box 48)
  - Pa-Pe (Box 48)
  - Patrick, Fred (Box 48)
  - Peer, Ronald (Box 48)
  - Perkins, Michael (Box 48-49)
  - Perlman, John (Box 49)
  - Perrone, Stephen (Box 49)
  - Peterson, Sue Councilor (Box 49)
  - Pew, Alfred (Box 49)
  - Ph-Pr (Box 50)
  - Phillips, Beth (Box 50)
  - Pines, Paul (Box 50)
  - Pinney, Theodore C. (Box 50)
  - The Poetry Center (San Francisco) (Box 51)
  - Poetry in Public Places (New York NY) (Box 51)
  - Pollet, Sylvester (Box 51)
  - Prince, Libby (Box 51)
  - Prues, Don (Box 51)
  - Pu (Box 51)
  - Q (Box 51)
  - R (Box 51)
  - R-Ra (Box 51)
  - Rattier, Rochelle (Box 51)
  - Randies, John & Beverly S. (Box 51)
  - Re-Ri (Box 51)
  - The Red Ozier Press (New York NY) (Box 51)
  - Redel, Victoria (Box 51)
  - Richards, Eric (Box 52)
  - Ro-Ru (Box 52)
  - Rogers, Evelyn G. (Box 52)
  - Ross, Robert H. (Box 52)
  - Rotella, Guy L. (Box 52)
  - Royal, Richard Everett (Box 52)
  - Rudman, Elizabeth (Box 52)
  - Rudman, Mark (Box 52)
  - Russell, Diarmuid (Russell & Volkening, Inc.; Literary Agents) (Box 52)
  - Ryan, Dennis (Box 52)
  - S (Box 53)
  - Sa-Se (Box 53)
  - Salerno, Mark (Box 53)
  - Samuels, Stephen Edmond (Box 53)
  - Sandresky, Clemens & Margaret (Box 54)
  - Schley, James P. (Box 54)
  - Schreur, Robert (Box 54)
  - Schultz, Harry Thomas (Box 54)
  - Schwartz, Leonard (Box 54)
  - Scotford, John Ryland (Box 55)
  - Sefcik, John W. (Box 55)
  - Seligson, Fred Jeremy (Box 55)
  - Seman, Larry (Box 55)
  - Sh-Si (Box 55)
  - Shaw, Chris (Box 55)
  - Sheaffer, Louis (Box 55)
  - Shetline, Leonard J. (Box 55)
  - Simmons, William Donald (Box 55)
  - Sk-Sp (Box 55)
  - Small Press Distribution, Inc. (Box 55)
  - Smith, C. Page (Box 55)
  - St-Sy (Box 56)
  - Stair, Gobin (Box 56)
  - Stark, Bradford (Box 56)
  - Stiles, Guy B. (Box 56)
  - Suberchicot, Alain (Box 56)
  - Sw (Box 56)
  - T (Box 56)
  - Tacon, Henri A. (Box 56)
  - Taggart, John (Box 56)
  - Tart, Keith (Box 57)
  - Taylor, Barbara I. (Box 57)
  - Townsend, Neil W. (Box 57)
  - U (Box 57)
  - Union College (Schenectady NY) (Box 57)
  - V (Box 57)
  - Vallarino, Barbara Cox & Joaquin Jose (Box 57)
  - W (Box 57)
  - Wa (Box 57)
  - Waldrop, Rosmarie & Keith (Box 57)
  - Walker, Scott (Box 57)
  - The Watershed Foundation (Washington DC) (Box 57)
  - Watson, Scott (Box 57)
  - We (Box 58)
  - Webster, Ronald (Box 58)
  - Weil, James L.
    - 1966-1974 (Box 58)
    - 1975-1979 (Box 59)
    - 1980-1987 (Box 60)
    - 1988-1992 (Box 61)
    - 1993-1999 (Box 62)
    - 1999-2000 (Box 63)
      (Letters to Weil about Bronk)
  - Weinberger, Eliot (Box 64)
  - Weinfield, Henry M. (Box 64)
  - Weiss, William (Box 65)
  - Wenrich, Douglass (Box 65)
  - Weseley, Matthew (Box 65)
  - Wh (Box 65)
  - Wheeler family (Box 65)
  - Whelen, Christopher (Box 65)
  - Wi-Wu (Box 65)
  - Williams, Henry B. (Box 65)
  - Williamson, Edward C. & Margaret W. (Box 66)
  - Wilson, John (Box 66)
  - Wolff, Daniel (Box 66)
  - Wolinsky, David (Box 66)
  - Worth, Douglas (Box 66)
  - Y (Box 66)
  - Yaddo (Saratoga Springs NY) (Box 66)
  - Z (Box 66)
  - Zigrosser, Carl & Laura C. (Box 66)
  - Zimmerman, Kenneth Graham (Box 66)
  - Zumbrun, W. Craig (Box 66)
  - Unidentified letters (Box 66)
- Series III: Uncataloged Manuscripts by William Bronk
  - A-B (Box 67)
  - The Brother in Elysium (Box 68)
  - B-F (Box 69)
  - F-G (Box 70)
  - H-M (Box 71)
  - M-O (Box 72)
  - O-R (Box 73)
  - S-T (Box 74)
  - U-Y (Box 75)
  - [Untitled Book Manuscripts] (Box 75)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 75)
  - Poetry Notebooks (Box 76)
- Series IV: Uncataloged Manuscripts by Others
  - The American Book Awards, 1982 (Box 77)
  - Auster, Paul (Box 77)
  - Bibliography [of William Bronk] (Box 77)
  - Bronk, Elizabeth (Box 77)
  - Bronk, Genevieve T. (Box 77)
  - Canadé, Eugene G. (Box 77)
  - Carella, Richard A. (Box 77)
  - Chawla, Louise (Box 77)
  - Chrisafides, Peter (Box 77)
  - Clark, Shirley (Box 78)
  - Clarke, Catherine (Box 78)
  - Clippinger, David W. & Annabelle Honza Clippinger (Box 78)
  - Collins, Ronald W. (Box 78)
  - Corman, Leonard (Box 78)
  - Corrigan, Paul (Box 78)
  - The Cuomo Inauguration, 1983 (Box 78)
  - Curran, Ann (Box 78)
  - Davis, Dale (Box 78)
  - Davis, Lydia (Box 78)
  - Di Piero, W. S. (Box 78)
  - Dobrin, Arthur (Box 78)
  - Dufault, Peter Kane (Box 78)
  - DuVall, Jack (Box 79)
  - Elman, Richard M. (Box 79)
  - Ernest, John Richard & Rebecca M. Ernest (Box 79)
  - Faivre, Rob (Box 80)
  - Feld, Ross (Box 80)
  - Finkelstein, Norman (Box 80)
  - Franck, Frederick (Box 80)
  - Gach, Gary G. (Box 80)
  - Gilmore, Charles Randall (Box 80)
  - Granville, Alan P. (Box 80)
  - Grealish, Gerard (Box 80)
  - Greene, Jonathan (Box 80)
  - Haberman, Daniel (Box 81)
  - Jama, Stephen (Box 81)
  - Jasper, Paul (Box 81)
  - Katz, David M. (Box 81)
  - Katzman, Mark (Box 81)
  - Kearns, Sherry (Box 81)
  - Keineg, Paol (Box 81)
  - Kerr, Don E. (Box 81)
  - Kimmelman, Burt (Box 82)
  - Lape, Walter (Box 83)
  - Leary, Daniel (Box 83)
  - Lyman, Henry (Box 83)
  - McDonald, Christine (Box 83)
  - Martin, William (Box 83)
  - Matthews, William (Box 83)
  - Mitchell, Stephen (Box 83)
  - Moore, Sherry (Box 83)
  - Morrisette, Mary (Box 83)
  - Morse, Samuel French (Box 83)
  - Murphy, Robert (Box 83)
  - Oderman, Kevin (Box 83)
  - Perkins, Michael (Box 84)
  - Perlman, John (Box 84)
  - Pines, Paul (Box 84-85)
  - Redel, Victoria (Box 86)
  - Roditi, Edouard (Box 86)
  - Royal, Richard Everett (Box 86)
  - Ryan, Dennis (Box 86)
  - Samuels, Steven Edmond (Box 86)
  - Schley, Jim (Box 87)
  - Schreur, Robert (Box 87)
  - Schultz, Harry Thomas (Box 87)
  - Schwartz, Frederic (Box 87)
  - Seligson, Fred J. (Box 87)
  - Shetline, Leonard J. (Box 87)
  - Stair, Gobin (Box 87)
  - Stark, Bradford (Box 87)
  - Stiles, Guy B. (Box 88)
  - Stolmar, Thomas Michael (Box 88)
  - Taggart, John (Box 88)
  - U.S. Army (Box 88)
  - U.S. Passports (Box 88)
  - Viera, John (Box 88)
  - Webster, Ronald (Box 88)
  - Weinfield, Henry (Box 89)
  - Weiss, William (Box 89)
  - Wenrich, Douglass (Box 89)
  - Wolff, Daniel (Box 89)
  - Worth, Douglas (Box 89)
  - Zion Church Sunday School Roll Book (Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous art work (Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous unidentified (Box 89)
- Series V: Photographs and Tape Cassettes
  - (Box 90)
- Series VI: Printed Materials
  - 1908-1938 undated (Box 91)
  - 1938-1969 (Box 92)
  - 1970-1980 (Box 93)
  - 1981-1984 (Box 94)
  - 1985-1998 (Box 95)
- Series VII: Oversized Materials
  - Scrapbook: photographs and newspaper clippings (Box Flat Box 287)
  - Adirondack Calendar (month of August ), 1989 August (Box Flat Box 287)
  - Hoefer Scientific Instruments, calendar, 1977 (Box Flat Box 287)
  - "The Fragile Endurance of the World" (Box Flat Box 287)